Okay the next exercise we're going to do with the medicine ball, and we're going to work again in tandem, two people, it's called the kick toss.
It's not as easy as it looks.
What we're going to do is we're going to have Guy get down on his back.
What I'm going to do is I'm going to actually toss it to guy.
Guy is going to load it up on to his ankle area of his feet and toss it back up to me.
Whereas I'm going to catch it and then return it back to him again.
So this is building his calves, his eye hand coordination while he's catching it, he's loading it, he's tossing it back up to me.
So we're getting quite a bit of different work outs here.
So I'm tossing it to Guy.
He's going to load it.
He's going to toss it up into the air and I'm going to catch it. Okay. He's going to load it and he's going to toss it straight up, okay?
As high as we can get it.
There we go.
So I toss it back to him.
He loads it.
He tosses it back up to me.
I toss it to him, he loads it.
Toss it back.
Kick toss.
There we go.
Okay Guy.
What do you feel that that's working for you.
It's working my ab, it's getting my inner thigh, calves.
It's pretty good.
Full lower body work out.
The kick toss.